<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <string name="about_dialog_title">About MandelSplit</string>
    <string name="about_dialog_msg">
Author and Copyright: Johannes Gajdosik, 2014\n\n

<b>MandelSplit</b>: A graphical visualizer for the Mandelbrot set
(see <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mandelbrot_set">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mandelbrot_set</a>)
which aims to be fast and deep.\n\n
+deep: IEEE754 64bit floating point artithmetic, maximum number of iterations &gt; 1000000.\n
+fast: uses all processor cores, avoids recalculation and unnecessary calculation of black pixels whenever possible.\n\n

That implies it will <b><i>drain your battery</i></b>.
By the way: <b><i>calculation will continue while the program is in the background</i></b>.\n\n

This is free software, meaning you do not have to pay, and it is free of ads,
malware, fishy permissions, in-app purchase and so on.
I plan to release it under GPL license later, but up to now I was too lazy for
setting up the repository.\n\n

Help, contributions and feedback is always welcome, especially:\n
+Suggestions and/or design and/or code, especially for user interface\n
+Vectorized 64bit calculation code for arm architecture - I am unsure if this is even possible\n
+positive reviews on google play\n\n

You can also tell me what additional features you would like to see, like:\n
*higher precision arithmethic (meaning you will be able to zoom in even more)\n
*Julia set\n\n

Do not hesitate to send me an email.\n\n

Yours,\n
Johannes Gajdosik

    </string>
    <string name="help_dialog_msg">
Any settings can be changed even while calculation is running:\n\n

Drag/Pinch/Spread/Turn to choose what you want to see.
Turning (aka Rotation) must be enabled in the settings.\n\n

Longpress or tap (or press the Menu button on Android 2.3)
to bring up the\n<b>Settings Dialog</b>:\nHere you can change the
maximum number of iterations up to 1048576.
If you have chosen this value too high, you can always press
\"minimize max iter\" in the dialog. This will set the value to 1+ the maximum value
of all non-black pixels - and hereby give nicer colors.



    </string>
</resources>

